bossventure.com 2012-12-30

# Terms and Conditions| BossVenture.com

**1\. INCORPORATION OF PRIVACY POLICY**

1.1 CASH DEAL SDN BHD (Company Number 929192-K) ('Company') is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and the Company is compliant with the Data Protection Act 2010 of Malaysia. This privacy policy ('Privacy Policy') explains how the Company uses the information that the Company collects about you and the procedures that the Company has in place to safeguard your privacy.

1.2 By using the Company's website http://www.BossVenture.com. ('Website'), acquiring any products ('Products') or services ('Services') via the Website, you consent to the Company using the information the Company collects about you. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set out in this Privacy Policy, do not continue to use the Website.

**2\. THE INFORMATION THE COMPANY COLLECTS AND HOW THE COMPANY USES IT**

2.1 When you visit the Website and/or, join the Website as a VIP Shopper and/or a Licensee, the Company may collect information including your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number , Products and/or Services obtained and/or supplied by you and such other relevant information which the Company deems necessary for the purpose of your obtaining and/or supplying the Product and/or Services and our providing maintenance and support services. Where necessary, the information collected is transmitted in a secure manner to third parties to assist the Company with your obtaining and/or supplying the Products and/or Services and for our providing maintenance support services . 

2.2 Subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, the Company protects all personal and financial data from being disclosed to any unauthorised third parties except when required by law. In addition, the Company may use your information to assist in the prevention of unlawful activities e.g. money laundering or activities which threaten the Company's Website or is adverse to your or the Company's interest.

2.3 The Company may also use aggregate information and statistics, (but, which will not contain your identifying information) for the purposes of monitoring your usage of the Website in order to help the Company develop the Website and the Products and/or Services offered by you and/or the Company. The Company may provide such aggregate information to third parties.

2.4 The Company may collect information which is based upon your behavior and navigation on the Website. This information allows the Company to carry out internal research on the users' interest, demographics and behavior so that the Company can better understand, and in turn provide better information, products and services to you and other customers or members.

2.5 The Company may also wish to provide you with information about special features featured on the Website or any other service or products the Company thinks may be of interest to you.

2.6 The Company may also want to provide you with related information from third parties which the Company thinks may be of interest to you.

2.7 If you do not wish the Company to send you any information set out in Clauses 2.5 and 2.6 above, please send an e-mail to info@bossventure.com. 

2.8 Subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Policy and such other provisions specified on the Website, the Company will not provide your information to other companies or organisations without your consent.

**3\. USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER INFORMATION GATHERING TECHNOLOGIES**

3.1 The Company uses 'cookies' and other technologies to collect information on site to assist the Company in monitoring the Company's web page flow, promotional effectiveness as well as to promote trust and safety.

3.2 Certain features on the Website are only available if you enable the cookie. The Company also uses cookies to assist the Company to provide information which is relevant to your interest.

3.3 You are free to decline the Company's cookies although that may impair certain features on the Website.

3.4 You can delete any cookies from your computer - refer to your internet browser's help files.

3.5 The Company may also track certain information through the use of JavaScript code and third party web site analytics providers.

**4\. PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

4.1 The internet is not a secure medium. However, the Company has put in place various security procedures and strict policy rules to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorised and unlawful access and use. These security procedures and policies are of high standards and are continuously improved.

4.2 Be that as it may, it should be appreciated that no system is entirely fool-proof and you should be careful when you reveal any confidential information to any third party.

**5\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

5.1 If the Company and/or part of its business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to the Company's advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the Company.

5.2 The Company reserves the right to disclose your data (and you consent to such disclosure) if the Company is under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply the Company's Terms of Use of the Website and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, the Company's customers or members. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**6\. ACCESSING AND/OR UPDATING YOUR DETAILS**

6.1 Any of the information you have provided to the Company is accessible by you. If any of the information that you have provided to the Company changes or is incorrect, for example if you wish to change or correct your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your membership, please inform the Company accordingly by sending an e-mail to info@bossventure.com.

**7\. OTHER TERMS**

7.1 The Company supplies links to other websites. If you click on a link, you are not protected by this Privacy Policy and you are advised to read the privacy policy of the other website as they may differ from this Privacy Policy.

7.2 The Company reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time as it deems necessary. In such event, the Company will post such changes on the Website.

7.3 The Company welcomes your views about the Website and its privacy policy. If you would like to contact the Company with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to info@bossventure.com.
